Finding aid for Interlochen Center for The Arts Records, 1927-2005
Bentley Historical Library
- Chronological, 1920-1966
  - Camp History papers
    - National Music Camp
      - 1927-1934, 8 folders (Box 2)
      - January-August, 1935
        - Camp-operations (Box 2)
        - Camper survey (Box 2)
        - Maddy-Giddings-Tremaine communications (Box 2)
        - National Music Clinic (Box 2)
        - Scherzo ad, American Book Company (Box 2)
    - Pennington family, circa, 1900-1968
      - History, circa, 1900-1927 (Box 2)
      - Purchase of Pennington property, 1931-1932 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1939-1968 (Box 2)
        - 1939-1940 (Box 2)
        - 1941 (Box 2)
        - 1942 (Box 2)
        - 1943 (Box 2)
        - 1944 (Box 2)
        - 1945 (Box 2)
        - 1946-1968 (Box 2)
      - Camp Penn Loch, printed, 1931-1941 (Box 2)
      - Camp Interlochen, printed, 1933-1943 (Box 2)
  - Camp files, 1935-1945
    Camp files, 1935-1945, consists mainly of Maddy's correspondence concerning the administration of the Camp, as maintained by Maddy and whoever happened to be his secretary at the time (his first wife Marie until 1937, John M. Lewis until 1938, Helen Hollingsworth until 1941, and Margaret "Peg" Stace thereafter). Its organization reflects the various filing systems of their creators and the seasonal nature of the Camp (with the office being located in Ann Arbor most of the year and then, transferred to Interlochen for the summer). A good overview of decisions regarding the Camp can be found in the correspondence of Giddings and Tremaine. Items of a personal nature on Maddy are usually filed under his name.
    Matters covered in this subseries involve students, parents, staff, faculty, and guest conductors as well as the courses and programs offered, acquisition of instruments and music (including relationships with manufacturers and publishers), maintenance and improvement of facilities, and use of advertising and promotion. Documentation is provided on the introduction of instruction in dance, drama, broadcasting, and art and in such instruments as the saxophone and accordion. Information is also supplied on Maddy's dispute with the publishers association on gifts of music to educational institutions.
    Problems of the Depression are highlighted along with the wartime difficulties of operating the Camp with government controls and limited enrollments (especially the shortage of college age males). Camper and former Camper correspondence provides personal experiences with economic hardship and military service. Pre-war faculty applications reflect the immigration to America of European musicians, many of them Jewish, while wartime files refer to the substitution of women musicians for men, including the development of "all girl" orchestras.
    - 1935-1936
      - A-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Advertising: M. E. Symonds (Box 3)
      - American Bandmasters' Association convention (Box 3)
      - Applications: faculty and staff (Box 3)
      - B-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Balliett, Melvin (Box 3)
      - Boutwell, William-re CCC radio (Box 3)
      - C-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Camp-operations (Box 3)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 3)
      - Caretaker-re construction and maintenance (Box 3)
      - D-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Damrosch Choir (Box 3)
      - Delta Omicron convention (Box 3)
      - Dietician-re food and staff (Box 3)
      - E-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Eastman School-re possible affiliation (Box 3)
      - Equipment, apparel, etc. (Box 3)
      - F-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Faculty-contracts (Box 3)
      - Faculty-impressions of Camp (Box 3)
      - Fischer, Carl-publisher (Box 3)
      - G-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - H-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Illinois State University-Emma Knudson (Box 3)
      - Julliard-scholarship aid (Box 3)
      - K-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - L-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - M-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Maddy-personal, including Marie's letters (Box 3)
      - Martin Band Instruments-re saxophones (Box 3)
      - Music Guild Productions-re instructional movie (Box 3)
      - N-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - O-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - P-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Part time workers (Box 3)
      - Printing Products Corporation (Box 3)
      - Publicity (Box 3)
      - R-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Royalties (Camp) (Box 3)
      - S-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Scherzo-yearbook ads (Box 3)
      - Staff (Box 3)
      - T-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Traverse City Chamber of Commerce (Box 3)
      - Tremaine
        - August-November 1935 (Box 3)
        - December 1935-February 14, 1936 (Box 3)
        - February 15-June, 1936 (Box 3)
      - V-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - W-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - Wurlitzer, Rudolph Company (Box 3)
    - Camp, 1936
      - A-L-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - M-Z-general correspondence (Box 3)
      - American Bandmasters' Association convention (Box 3)
      - Belstrom, Chester (Camp director) (Box 3)
      - Camp-preparations (Box 3)
      - Camp closing-procedures (Box 3)
      - Camp schedules (Box 3)
      - Damrosch Choir (Box 3)
      - Equipment-apparel (Box 3)
      - Faculty-general (Box 3)
      - Fischer, Carl, Inc. (Box 3)
      - Hotel (Box 3)
      - Illinois State University (Box 3)
      - Library (Box 3)
      - Medical (Box 3)
      - Music Publishers Association (Box 3)
      - National Music Clinic-contest lists (Box 3)
      - Planning-Camp for, 1937 (Box 3)
      - Programs-mimeographed and posters (Box 3)
      - Publicity
        - General (Box 3)
        - Movies (commercial) (Box 3)
        - Press releases (Box 3)
      - Rosters-Campers (Box 3)
      - Saxophone instruction-Fred Holtz of Martin Band Instrument Co. (Box 3)
      - Scherzo-yearbook music ads (Box 3)
      - Scholarship awards (Box 3)
      - Tremaine (Box 3)
      - Visitors
        - General (Box 3)
        - Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 3)
    - 1936-1937
      - A-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Accordion instruction (Box 4)
      - Advertising (Box 4)
      - B-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - C-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Camp-operations (Box 4)
      - Campers, Parents, and Friends (Box 4)
      - Caretaker (Bruce Maynard) (Box 4)
      - Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 4)
      - D-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - E-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Equipment (Box 4)
      - F-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Faculty
        - Applications (Box 4)
        - Contracts (Box 4)
        - Correspondence (Box 4)
      - Fischer, Carl Inc. (Box 4)
      - Fischer, J. & Bro.-re Afro-American Symphony (Box 4)
      - Foster, Stephen Memorial Foundation (Box 4)
      - G-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Giddings (Box 4)
      - Gifts and scholarships (Box 4)
      - H-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - I-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Illinois State University (Box 4)
      - J-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - K-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - L-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Library (Box 4)
      - M-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 4)
      - Music Guild Productions-re instructional movie (Box 4)
      - Muskegon Centennial Concert (Box 4)
      - N-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - National Education Association (Box 4)
      - P-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Pi Lambda Theta convention (Box 4)
      - Piano tuning (J. Clark Rhodes) (Box 4)
      - Publicity/Promotion
        - Correspondence (Box 4)
        - Papers (Box 4)
      - R-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 4)
      - S-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Saxophone instruction (Box 4)
      - Staff (Box 4)
      - T-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Tremaine (Box 4)
      - W-general correspondence (Box 4)
    - Camp, 1937
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Camp-courses (Box 4)
      - Camp-schedules (Box 4)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 4)
      - Faculty-papers (Box 4)
      - Full time staff (Box 4)
      - Hammond Organ Co. (Box 4)
      - Insurance analysis (by Stock agency) (Box 4)
      - Instruments and equipment (Box 4)
      - Klein, Maynard (Box 4)
      - Library (Box 4)
      - Maddy-personal recommendations (Box 4)
      - Muskegon Centennial Concert (Box 4)
      - Part time staff (Box 4)
      - Planning for Camp (Box 4)
      - Programs (Box 4)
      - Prospect form letters (Box 4)
      - Publicity
        - Print (Box 4)
        - Movie (Box 4)
      - Publishers (Box 4)
      - Rosters-Camper and staff (Box 4)
      - Scholarships (Box 4)
      - Traverse City (Box 4)
      - Tremaine (Box 4)
      - Visitors (Box 4)
    - 1937-1938
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 4)
      - Accordion instruction (Box 4)
      - American Book Co.-re Scherzo ad (Box 4)
      - Belstrom, Chester (Camp director) (Box 4)
      - Boutwell, William-re Radio Workshop (Box 4)
      - Camp-operations (Box 4)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 4)
      - Equipment (Box 4)
      - Faculty (Box 4)
      - Giddings (Box 4)
      - Hammond Organ Co. (Box 4)
      - Hollingsworth, Helen (Camp secretary) (Box 4)
      - Hotel-operations/staff (Box 4)
      - Illinois State University (Box 4)
      - Lewis, John (Camp secretary) (Box 4)
      - Library (Box 5)
      - Maddy-personal
        - Divorce (Box 5)
        - Indiana U. deanship application (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
        - Traverse City Cannery (Box 5)
      - Prospects/inquiries-re Campers (Box 5)
      - Publicity
        - Print (Box 5)
        - Movie (Box 5)
      - Publishers-re. music donations (Box 5)
      - Recorder (instrument) instruction (Box 5)
      - Reunion-Camper luncheon at MENC convention (Box 5)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 5)
      - Saxophone instruction (Box 5)
      - Scherzo advertising
        - Future (Box 5)
      - Scholarships
        - General (Box 5)
        - National High School Orchestra members (Box 5)
      - Staff (Box 5)
      - Tremaine (Box 5)
      - World's Fair (Olin Downes) (Box 5)
    - Camp, 1938
      - A-L, general correspondence (Box 5)
      - M-Z-general correspondence (Box 5)
      - Accordion instruction (Clark Fortner) (Box 5)
      - Art instruction (Meinzinger Art School) (Box 5)
      - Camp-operations (Box 5)
      - Camp book (Box 5)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 5)
      - Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 5)
      - Faculty (Box 5)
      - Fourth of July performance (Box 5)
      - Guest conductors (Box 5)
      - Hammond Organ Co. (Box 5)
      - Hotel (Helen McBride) (Box 5)
      - Illinois State University (Box 5)
      - Library-re instruments, music, etc. (Box 5)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 5)
      - Medical reports (Box 5)
      - Planning-recommendations for Camp (Box 5)
      - Publicity (Box 5)
      - R.C.A.-re. recordings (Box 5)
      - Rosters-girls camp directory (Box 5)
      - Scherzo
        - Announcement-end of advertising (Box 5)
        - List of advertisers, 1928-1936 (Box 5)
      - Scholarships and other gifts
        - Donations-Camp (Box 5)
        - Awards-Camp
          - General (Box 5)
          - Saxophone (Box 5)
        - College and conservatory awards (Box 5)
      - Staff
        - General (Box 5)
        - Full time workers (Box 5)
        - Part time workers (Box 5)
      - Tremaine (Box 5)
      - Visitors (Box 5)
      - World's Fair (Box 5)
    - 1938-1939
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 5)
      - Accordion instruction (Box 5)
      - Advertising and promotions (Box 5)
      - Arnaud, William E.-copyright assignment (Box 5)
      - Bache/Stefany-possible gift (Box 5)
      - Belstrom, C. E. (Camp director) (Box 5)
      - Boutwell, William (Radio workshop) (Box 5)
      - Camper Alumni and Parents (Box 5)
      - Equipment (Box 5)
      - Faculty
        - Contracts (Box 5)
        - Correspondence (Box 5)
      - Giddings (Box 5)
      - Hammond Organ (Box 5)
      - Hollingsworth/Maddy communications (Box 5)
      - Hotel (Ben Atherton, manager) (Box 5)
      - Insurance (G. W. Power) (Box 5)
      - Illinois State University (Box 5)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 5)
      - Northwestern University-possible affiliation (Box 5)
      - Pre-camp planning (Box 5)
      - Prospects
        - College division (Box 5)
        - High school division (Box 5)
      - Publicity
        - General (Box 5)
        - Luncheons to promote Camp (Box 5)
      - Radio Corporation of America-re recording equipment (Box 5)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 5)
      - Scholarships
        - General (Box 5)
        - National Association of Broadcasters (Box 5)
        - Saxophone (Box 5)
      - Schramm, Rudolph (possible Music Teachers National Association talk) (Box 5)
      - Sousa Memorial (Box 5)
      - Schwarz, Boris and Joseph (faculty) (Box 5)
      - Southland Symphony (Box 5)
      - Staff correspondence (Box 5)
      - Tonette (new instrument) (Box 5)
      - Tremaine (Box 6)
      - World's Fair
        - Financial
          - State legislature and other (Box 6)
          - Parents (Box 6)
        - Railroad transportation (Box 6)
    - Camp, 1939
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 6)
      - Camp-operations (Box 6)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 6)
      - La Prade, Ernest (guest conductor) (Box 6)
      - Library (Box 6)
      - Publicity (Box 6)
      - Radio workshop-scripts (Box 6)
      - Scholarships (Box 6)
      - Store (Camp) (Box 6)
      - Traverse City (Box 6)
      - Tremaine (Box 6)
      - United Artists-re Jasha Heifitz movie (Box 6)
      - World's Fair
        - Arrangements (Box 6)
        - Performances (Box 6)
        - Newspaper articles (Box 6)
    - 1939-1940
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 6)
      - Advertising/promotion (Box 6)
      - Art (Meinzinger Art School) (Box 6)
      - Belstrom, C. E. (Camp director) (Box 6)
      - Boutwell, W. D. (radio workshop) (Box 6)
      - Camp-operations (Box 6)
      - Caretaker (Cliff Hiatt) (Box 6)
      - Carnegie Foundation music set (Box 6)
      - Choir (Noble Cain) (Box 6)
      - Clarinets, Mezzo (Box 6)
      - Conventions and meetings at Interlochen (Box 6)
      - Dance (Hildegard Lewis and Francis Wright) (Box 6)
      - Dietician (Anne Haggerty) (Box 6)
      - Drama (Douglas Ferguson) (Box 6)
      - Faculty
        - Applications (Box 6)
        - Correspondence, A-M (Box 6)
        - Correspondence, N-Z (Box 6)
      - Giddings (Box 6)
      - Guest conductors (Box 6)
      - Hammond Organ Co. (Box 6)
      - Hollingsworth/Maddy correspondence (Box 6)
      - Hotel (Ben Atherton) (Box 6)
      - Illinois State University (Box 6)
      - Lecturers, requests from (Box 6)
      - Library (Norman Goldberg) (Box 6)
      - Maddy-personal
        - General (Box 6)
        - Michigan State College job application (Box 6)
      - Morrow, Veda (American Woman's Association) (Box 6)
      - Planning-Camp
        - Opening (Box 6)
        - Schedules (Box 6)
      - Publicity
        - Print (Box 6)
        - Movie-Camp
          - Production (Charles T. Chapman) (Box 6)
          - Showings (Box 6)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 6)
      - Scholarships (Box 6)
      - Schwarz, Boris (Faculty-violin) (Box 6)
      - Southland Symphony (Box 6)
      - Staff (Box 6)
      - Traverse City Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
      - Tremaine (Box 6)
      - West Michigan Tourist Association (Box 6)
      - World's Fair (Box 6)
      - Wurlitzer, Rudolph Co. (Box 6)
    - Camp, 1940
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 7)
      - Agent contracts (Box 7)
      - Alumni week (Box 7)
      - Camp-operations (Box 7)
      - Campers and Parents (Box 7)
      - Choir (Box 7)
      - College Division fees (Box 7)
      - Concert receipts (Box 7)
      - Delta Omicron medal (Box 7)
      - Dietician (Anne Haggerty) (Box 7)
      - Equipment (Box 7)
      - Giddings (Box 7)
      - Grant, Allen (Southland Symphony) (Box 7)
      - Guest conductors (Box 7)
      - Insurance for Campers (Box 7)
      - Library (publishers) (Box 7)
      - Maddy-notes (Box 7)
      - Publicity
        - Campers (Box 7)
        - Saturday Evening Post article (Box 7)
        - Movie-Camp (Chapman) (Box 7)
      - Prospects for, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Radio workshop (Box 7)
      - Regulations re uniforms (Box 7)
      - Report forms-high school campers (Box 7)
      - Scholarships
        - General (Box 7)
        - Ticket sales: Benzonia, Beulah, Cadillac (Box 7)
      - Scripts: Bowl programs continuity (Box 7)
      - Tremaine (Box 7)
    - 1940-1941
      - A-H-general correspondence (Box 7)
      - J-Z-general correspondence (Box 7)
      - Advertising (N. W. Ayer & Son) (Box 7)
      - Art (Box 7)
      - Belstrom, C. E. (Camp supt.-resignation) (Box 7)
      - Camp-operations (Box 7)
      - Campers-former: correspondence (Box 7)
      - Caretaker (C. G. Hiatt) (Box 7)
      - College Division (Box 7)
      - Crescendo-replies on autographed copies (Box 7)
      - Dance (Hildegard Lewis) (Box 7)
      - Dietician (Viola Walberg) (Box 7)
      - Drama (Box 7)
      - Equipment (Box 7)
      - Faculty
        - Applications (Box 7)
        - Correspondence (Box 7)
      - Giddings (Box 7)
      - Grant, Allen (Southland Symphony) (Box 7)
      - Form letters re Camp (Box 7)
      - Hopping family (U.S. Attorney, Camper, and parents) (Box 7)
      - Illinois State University (Box 7)
      - Insurance on Campers (Gnau) (Box 7)
      - Library (Box 7)
      - Loomis, Edwin C. (opera composer) (Box 7)
      - MacGowan, Leroy (Boys Camp director) (Box 7)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 7)
      - Norman, Francis (Girls Camp director) (Box 7)
      - Pere Marquette Railroad (Box 7)
      - Phi Sigma Nu convention (Box 7)
      - Private lessons for non-Campers (Box 7)
      - Publicity and Promotion
        - General (Box 7)
        - Movie-Camp (Chapman) (Box 7)
      - Publishers (Box 7)
      - Radio workshop (Box 7)
      - Recommendations for individuals (Box 7)
      - Recordings (Box 7)
      - Requests, miscellaneous (Box 7)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 7)
      - Saxophone (Box 7)
      - Scholarships (Box 7)
    - 1940-1941
      - Staff
        - Applications (Box 7)
        - Full time-contracts (Box 7)
        - Part time (student) (Box 7)
      - Store-Camp (Box 7)
      - Tremaine, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Voice (Box 7)
      - Wurlitzer (accordion) (Box 7)
    - Camp, 1941
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 7)
      - Alumni-rates (Box 7)
      - Boys Camp (Box 7)
      - Camp-operations (Box 7)
      - Camper parent complaints (Box 7)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 7)
      - College Division (Box 7)
      - Conventions and meetings (Box 7)
      - Cranks and oddities (Box 7)
      - Faculty (Box 7)
      - Frankfort (Michigan) concert (Box 7)
      - Girls Camp (Box 7)
      - Gubernatorial letters-re state flags (Box 7)
      - Guest conductors (Box 7)
      - Guitar teachers-re possible visit (Box 7)
      - High school band performances (Box 8)
      - Illinois State University (Box 8)
      - Insurance for Campers (Gnau) (Box 8)
      - Interlochen Every Week (newsletter) (Box 8)
      - Inventories (Hotel and Medical) (Box 8)
      - Klein, Maynard (Box 8)
      - Library (music and instruments) (Box 8)
      - Mackinac Island Festival re appearance (Box 8)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 8)
      - N.R.A.-re rifle instruction (Box 8)
      - National Youth Administration-Michigan orchestra, Camp project (Box 8)
      - Orchestra Camp (All State and Region 3)-re cancellation (Box 8)
      - Programs-Camp performances (Box 8)
      - Publicity releases (Box 8)
      - Questionnaires-on how learned of Camp
        - High School Boys (Box 8)
        - High School Girls (Box 8)
        - College Division (Box 8)
      - Radio Department (Box 8)
      - Recommendations for 1942-Camp (Box 8)
      - Recommendations requested-individuals (Box 8)
      - Recording (Stock broadcast) (Box 8)
      - Reports on Camp (Box 8)
      - Rosters for Girls Camp (Box 8)
      - Royalties (Box 8)
      - Scholarships (Box 8)
      - Scripts for performances
        - Band (Radio Department) (Box 8)
        - College orchestra (Box 8)
        - Dance (Box 8)
        - Faculty (Box 8)
        - High school orchestra (Box 8)
        - Student (Box 8)
      - Season passes (Box 8)
      - Staff meeting (Box 8)
      - Store-Camp (Box 8)
      - Supplies (Box 8)
      - Tourist associations (Box 8)
      - Traverse City-Cherry Festival (Box 8)
      - Vandenbosch, T. C. (composer) (Box 8)
    - 1941-1942
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 8)
      - Accordion instruction (Box 8)
      - Accounts receivable (Box 8)
      - Advertising (Box 8)
      - Awards: Sinfonia and Delta Omicron-outstanding boy and girl Camper (Box 8)
      - Boys Camp (Box 8)
      - Buschert, Mrs. Helen-re scholarship concert (Box 8)
      - Camp-operations (Box 8)
      - Camp-weekly magazine (discontinued) (Box 8)
      - Camp Penn Loch (Junior Boys) (Box 8)
      - Campers correspondence
        - Past summer (Box 8)
        - Previous (Box 8)
      - Caretaker (Hiatt and Curtiss) (Box 8)
      - College Division inquiries (Box 8)
      - Dietitian-supplies and workers (Box 8)
      - Faculty
        - Applications (Box 8)
        - Biographies (Box 8)
        - Correspondence (Box 8)
      - Foto-Lith Co.-re printing (Box 8)
      - Giddings (Box 8)
      - Girls Camp (Box 8)
      - Guest conductors (Box 8)
      - Hammond Organ Company (Box 8)
      - Hoffmaster, Maud (art) (Box 8)
      - Hotel (Box 8)
      - Illinois All State Orchestra (Box 8)
      - Illinois State University (Box 8)
      - Insurance (Box 8)
      - Kjos, Neil (publisher and distributor) (Box 8)
      - Library (Box 8)
      - MacGowan, William (Camp director) (Box 8)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 8)
      - Medical-staff (Box 8)
      - Milwaukee luncheon (Wesley and Weisbrod) (Box 8)
      - National Youth Administration (Box 8)
      - Pere Marquette Railway (Box 8)
      - Photography (Box 8)
      - Prospects-Campers (Box 8)
      - Publicity
        - Print (James Haswell) (Box 8)
        - Movie (Chapman) (Box 8)
      - Radio Department (Box 8)
      - Royalties-Camp (Box 8)
      - Scholarships (Box 8)
      - Stace/Maddy correspondence (Box 8)
      - Southland Symphony (Box 8)
      - Staff
        - Correspondence-job offers (Box 8)
        - Full time (Box 8)
        - Part time (Box 8)
      - Store-Camp (Box 8)
      - Supplies for Camp (Box 8)
      - Swensen, Grace-Camper/staff (Box 8)
      - Tremaine, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Traverse City Chamber of Commerce (Box 8)
      - Visitors-invitations (Box 8)
    - Camp, 1942
      - A-Z-general correspondence (Box 9)
      - Alumni correspondence (Box 9)
      - Awards-Sinfonia and Delta Omicron (Box 9)
      - Buschert, Helen (Box 9)
      - Camp-operations (Box 9)
      - Caretaker (Curtiss dismissal) (Box 9)
      - Chicago concert proposal (Box 9)
      - Grinnell Bros. (organ dedication) (Box 9)
      - Guest conductors (Box 9)
      - Horton, Lewis Henry (composer) (Box 9)
      - Hotel (conventions) (Box 9)
      - Library (instruments and music) (Box 9)
      - Maddy-personal (Box 9)
      - Medical (report) (Box 9)
      - Minutes and reports (Box 9)
      - Private lessons for non-Campers (Box 9)
      - Programs (Interlochen Bowl) (Box 9)
      - Publicity (James Haswell) (Box 9)
      - Broadcast ban appeals (Box 9)
      - General (Box 9)
      - Press releases (Box 9)
      - Questionnaires-on how learned of Camp
        - Summary (Box 9)
        - Individual responses (Box 9)
      - Radio Department-guest panelists (Box 9)